### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/duxnguyen (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

web3

**NFT** 

User Experience (UX)

## Languages

English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Cybersecurity at Work

# Dux Nguyen

UI/UX Design Lead

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Summary

I am a Senior Designer specialized in Web, Mobile App Development, and UI/UX Design. I am honored to help my company get ADDY Award 2020, MUSE Creative Awards 2021 with my designs. My passion is to create unique products that improve digital user experiences and beautiful interactions that help drive interest. I have worked with top brands and continuously sharping my design skills to produce my best work.

MUSE Creative Awards 2021: 3 Platinum awards

ADDY Awards: 1 Gold Certificate, 1 Silver Certificate

If you are interested in learning more about my skills,

Please feel free to contact me at: My Email: namdu89@gmail.com

Telegram: @duxnguyen89 Phone: +84 39 999 3377

## Experience

Myria

2 years 10 months

**UX/UI** Design Lead

June 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)

I am working as Lead designer who is in charge of Myria's Ethereum Layer-2 product designs:

- Myria Design System, Homepage, Product Landing pages, Myria Game Campaign pages
- Myria platform: L2 Wallet, Web3 Marketplace, Ethereum L2 Nodes Dashboard, Developer Portal
- Myria Ecosystem: Aggregator DEX, Token Launchpad, Staking Platform

Senior UX/UI Designer
June 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Page 1 of 3

#### Remote

Impekable | Award-winning digital agency for enterprise clients worldwide

6 years 4 months

Senior UI/UX Designer - Project Design Lead March 2018 - June 2022 (4 years 4 months)

UI/UX Designer March 2016 - March 2018 (2 years 1 month) San Jose, Califonia

I am working at Impekable team as a full-time remote employee from Vietnam.

Ticketbox Vietnam
Product Design Lead
August 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 4 months)

I am working for Ticketbox as a freelance contractor to lead the project of Ticketbox redesign from mobile app, website portal, and event management dashboard, focus on Singapore market.

VNG Corporation UX/UI Designer August 2015 - March 2016 (8 months) Vietnam

I was a Design collaborator who worked directly with Zing Me Head of the department to helps the team design a mobile app as a social platform for gamers, Zing Play, from the very first stage.

DSquare I Square Group UI/UX Production Designer April 2015 - March 2016 (1 year) Vietnam

TMA Solutions
UX/UI Designer
February 2015 - March 2015 (2 months)

Young World Technology
Web UI/UX Designer
April 2014 - December 2014 (9 months)

FPT Online Web Designer December 2013 - April 2014 (5 months) Tan Thuan, Hochiminh city

Design for all products of Gate.vn project

Asiasoft Corporation Public Company Limited Web/Graphic Designer
October 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 3 months)

# Education

Hochiminh University of Science
Bachelor's degree, Networking · (2007 - 2012)